hey there this is bent from qscript and
welcome to another interesting lesson in
the tosa automation
playlist now in this particular session
I'm going to show you how you can
execute your test cases multiple times
from the execution list now we have
already seen how you can do this using
the reputations property inside your
test cases but if you don't want to do
this setting in your test cases rather
you want to do it during your executions
this is also possible uh through uh
setting a particular property for your
execution entry so let's see how we can
do this so I've got a particular test
case uh which is basically opening a URL
and then it is logging into that
particular website and then closing the
browser now I want to run this
particular test case multiple times now
as you can see uh I don't have any
folder and uh I don't have any
reputation property for any particular
folder inside this test case right so
that particular configuration is not
done here so it will not run multiple
times but if I want to directly do it at
an execution list level then uh I have
already created a execution list folder
and under that I have created a
execution list now if I drag this test
case into this execution list
that becomes a execution entry right and
for this particular execution entry if I
go into properties um I will find the
same property called reputations this is
also present uh at a test case folder
level okay but here I can then set the
number of repetition I want to do for
this particular execution entry
okay so now um if I want to run this
multiple times I can do this using the
repetition property at an execution
entry level rather than at a test case
level okay so now if I run this
execution folder you will see that it
will run three times instead of just
once
now if I expand this execution entry you
will see that uh it has done three
executions okay and uh obviously you can
always configure the values and use
different values for these three
different executions which you want to
do so uh reputation at uh execution
entry level is also possible apart from
what we have already seen earlier where
you can and repeat your test case
folders multiple
times that's all for this particular
video if you have any questions then
please leave it in the comments if you
like this video then please subscribe to
our Channel thanks for watching and I
will see you in the next
video